In witness the name of the king.
Public humiliation.
Public punishment.
Gather everyone in the square
public humiliation.
Are you tired?
We have not finished
in any case.
When you look stoned?
And ... there will be a
pleasant surprise.
And ... a unique experience
today, at Louisbourg.
We flogged ...
Not as ...
xanamastigothei in his life!
Long live the King!
Regret?
I see a lady
d like to try
whipping.
Does not?
No, please stop!
Please do not do it.
Do not do it!
No, I will not.
I came here to work, to
rebuild their brochure you.
But please,
do me a favor.
Put more power.
Louder.
Louder, louder!
Very well.
You have very audacity, sir.
RETURN ON HEARING:
CALAMITY JANE
Welcome to Montreal.
passengers with transit,
Please check the dashboard
any changes to
hours of departure.
I am glad. On the right hand side.
Thank you.
Hey.
Hi ...
I think I'm sitting here.
Sorry, I know you from ...?
Public humiliation.
Well, obviously ...
Not before? There you
I know from somewhere else?
Not from what I know.
Although my looks familiar.
Yes ...
Did you have an accident at Louisbourg;
- What?
- The wheelchair.
Something happened to your feet?
No ... I have just one problem ...
I can not walk over
than 5 minutes without help.
- Here.
- Thank you.
No, not you.
Pardon
Do not have an issue with your foot.
Well ...
Have to walk more
4 minutes around the castle.
And he gave me and understood when
it's time for the whipping.
Well, okay, now read.
No, not read.
I do not read.
Saw me sleeping.
You missed a spot. There.
Yeah, okay.
Milk!
Who orders
milk on airplanes?
Tomato juice, jerk, this
you order the plane!
"Dream for Hitler."
Includes
famous analysis ...
The whipping of feeling ...
Are you okay?
What are you reading?
I fear airports.
That's why you read about
Hitler in hits?
You want me to answer?
Flight fear response.
At airports.
Going from one
plane to another.
To run, to hurry
I do not know ...
Trying ... to find ...
To wonder if
will do it ...
What do you think will happen
if you do not succeed?
I think I might be lost ...
... And can
rot and die ...
In ... a forgotten
Empty Terminal ...
... Whose existence
no one knows.
And that the flight would lose you.
No ...
this is not the fear ...
Then what are you afraid of?
I fear the stress of
I wonder if you'll miss ...
I do not like to be here
the intermediate ...
I'm afraid to be afraid.
Sounds like the most
dangerous thing in the world.
Greetings.
We will make two stops ...
62, MacLaughlin Crescent,
close to Queen ...
Really?
Yes, because you where you live?
Very close, actually.
- I will walk out of there.
- Really?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Yes, why, where do you live?
Very close.
I am married.
Pity.
Pity, because I live here.
Shit.
Hey, baby.
I love you so much ...
Which ... will melt your head
the mill mashed ...
I love you so much,
that will put your spleen
minced his machine.
And it is
rusty machine.
I love you so much ...
That ... I'll do
injection in the face ...
with an awesome combination
from deadly viruses.
Won, it made me laugh.
What time will come by your own?
When they manage to put their
children in the car, so ..
Maybe ... in infinite time.
I look forward to seeing the little Tony.
It's very good.
I will play with her.
Will you do the monkey?
Nicely.
I will, really.
I want to play with Tony.
I know.
And I know.
I know already.
I'm going to bathe.
- Knock knock!
- Who is it?
- A starfish interrupting.
- What is.
Well, this. Do you understand?
Knock it off!
Jerry! Jerry!
Why do not you want to go the
Tony Montesoriani in School?
But I want to go!
- Lies!
- Speak clearly.
You want to do that work
a tavern princess?
Welcome to our restaurant.
Would you like some chicken?
It's okay, do not
hit really.
Thank you.
I do not like so the brie.
It's a little bland.
Bland!
Make sure to mark
what you do not like, Mom.
Indeed it does.
I'll take them.
It's all wonderful.
Thank you.
And I like people to serve.
And I like to
see you sit.
You deserve it.
I love these flowers.
I know it is not beautiful?
I'll tell you what does not help.
Every book you read
for that matter, says ...
for people
backslide 8 times ...
Well, I am well
honestly, but ...
This ... is the feeling that
are waiting to fail ...
You look very well.
I know.
Truth. Look in
mirror and want to fuck with.
I honestly believe that I look
better than before I gave birth to Tony.
Think about it?
Yes ... You look fantastic!
- Thank you.
It is from these moments that you want
Your answer to the other immediately.
I do not think it will fail.
Do not look at me like that.
With this sincere look ...
... Like a baby fawn.
The next time you wake up
inside me vomit ...
... You should feel
guilty about you.
Then do not do it.
Do not wake up in
in your vomit.
I put my best.
On Tuesday I will close 10 months.
Very nice!
Okay, enough.
Get off me.
Nobody died.
Being "the good
new ", you know?
Okay, guys, it's time.
Bye, sweetie!
- Goodbye!
- I love you so much.
- Thank you, aunt.
Take us somewhere.
Very French style yourself.
- Hi.
Do not even know what my
fix for breakfast.
I do not know what my
fix you breakfast!
What
What "what"?
Glad you're here.
Yes?
Yes.
- Bad baby.
- No, I am not a bad baby!
No?'re Not
evil baby? No.?
You look like the worst
baby in the world.
I'm not a bad baby,
I'm mad at you.
Are you mad
my baby?
Yes, I'm mad at you.
I love you, baby.
We can not play
"evil baby" anymore?
Do not kiss the time
we call such.
Merry.
Wait.
What
I will continue to
I make breakfast
and you continue to require
how to become everything.
I did not ...
Sorry.
Howdy.
Hi!
Where are you going?
At the grocery store.
Big breakfast?
Great breakfast, start early.
You mean because both
early in the grocery store.
No, no, just woke up.
Naturally.
What does this mean
Irritable, irritable lady.
Who needs a rickshaw
at 5 am, asshole?
I go to the lake
shortly before dawn.
And then I go straight to work.
It makes no sense ...
I just do not like to
I come home in between.
- You go to the lake?
- Yes.
To think?
Yes.
- This is so gay.
- Gay?
You adelfara.
What are you? 12 years old in 1982?
Who says that word anymore?
Who go every
morning on the lake?
Ego.
The sisters.
I think I woke up early
to insult me.
You think?
Nice talking to you ...
To do it again some
time to drink coffee.
- It is a call-shot?
- What?
It is an invitation-shoot
or a normal call?
Like, "had to ask him if he wants
drink coffee sometime ...
But ... I have no
intend to do. "
Significant difference from
normal call.
No, it is a call-shot.
Okay, then,
what about now?
Let the gay office
you for me.
Stop it.
So what will you do
Now with me?
What do you mean?
To "succeed" now.
What will you do?
To "succeed" now?
Yesterday I woke up early,
and saw me leave,
I do not "succeed" anywhere.
And now with "succeed."
Now what would you do?
Nothing.
Maybe simple is good ...
Talking normally ...
between us, so ...
That things ...
not be so ...
- ... charged?
- No, I did not say "charged".
- Well.
- I never said "charged".
Got it.
Can I show you something?
Well it would seem
bit like monitoring ..
But ... you're the one
he woke up at 5.30;
to follow me,
so ...
This ...
Causes me consternation ... basically ...
All right.
I guess my answer
is, "Fuck you".
What
One side is
full of hope.
Yes, but the other side
is a junkie,
ready to fountarei
a bridge.
No, you become melodramatic.
One side does not respond
rather the full dynamics.
The one on my side, or
one side of the picture?
Well ...
And ... it was very
good idea, obviously.
You want something to drink,
or another coffee ...?
No, no, no.
- Water?
- No, I must go.
Then why not do it?
So you're an artist.
Why do not you sit?
No, I paint.
What does this mean
It means that for paint
myself, and ...
... Pay my rent,
carrying the rickshaw ...
... Through the city streets, as
bum one of the modern era.
You show your work anywhere?
No.
Why
Because I'm a coward.
These are then.
- No.
- No?
I'm not sitting.
Merry.
What about you?
I want to write.
- You do?
- Not now. Not yet.
Write, but not those
I want to write.
But yeah.
Then why ...?
What prevents you?
What's wrong with you?
General.
You look worried.
I do not mean just now ...
I mean ... in general.
I remember when my niece,
The Tony was newborn ...
Reserving the ... ...
... And sometimes crying,
as do babies, and ...
And ... I did what I could
to find the cause.
Hungry, is tired?
Has rash?
9 times out of 10 I
solve the problem, but ...
Sometimes ... I do not know ...
Sometimes ...
I walk in the street, and ...
... A ray of light illuminates a
special way the sidewalk ...
And ... I want to cry ...
And ... after a
second over.
And I decide, because
I'm an adult.
Decide not to leave
the emotional moment.
and this some thought
times with Tony.
And she just lived
such a time.
One moment he did not know
how and why
and just let herself.
And he could not do
someone something about it.
To make it better.
He was alone.
And the fact that
're alive ...
Conflict ... with this ...
Yes.
Or just do not understand
what it was.
Yes.
I guess though
this is likely.
The fact that I met you.
Seems inevitable.
I think I saw
something in your eye.
No, I think I
I saw something in your eye.
Indeed I think
No, I saw something
in thine eye.
It's so weird, because ...
I was so sure
that you had something!
I guess that I'm wrong
got something in your eye.
Come on.
All right.
Lou!
We need to see this.
With rain and cold water.
Lou?
Yes?
- Do you have a job?
- Yes.
No.
I want to zoulixo until
I leave all the snot ..
I want to be raped
with scissors ...
Until they die ...
by bleeding.
Very far fetched.
Much? No, it was
far fetched
Will scratch the
grater for the potatoes.
Is that all?
This is silly.
It's scary!
Not in the grater
for potatoes.
When did you start to win
in this game?
I do not know.
Perhaps it means that now
I love you more.
I love you.
Why
I love most.
I really love you.
I love you.
I love ...
So ... much.
I can not in
love you so much.
Take me away.
Well, well. Careful.
- Bad time?
- Poor time.
When you make chicken must
carefully cleaned.
The groin their
are poisonous.
Where touch
let salmonella.
You're hot and sweaty.
I know, it's hot.
We need to cook at high
temperature for germs.
I missed you.
Me too.
It's lonely up there.
There are more solitary?
Did you get a dog?
A small dog.
Really?
I love dogs.
If you feel lonely, you
to have the dog.
The dog is like
preparation for a child.
No! Rather preparation
a cow.
Or a larger animal.
This one.
Usually, when a couple gets dog
two years to make and child.
Perhaps if we take a
very small dog,
make child 6
years, or something.
I do not want to discuss it.
You do not know how stupid I feel.
Come, my sweet,
not spoil me.
This is my joy.
Well, ladies,
look at me, okay!
What are ready to
rocking the pool?
My name is Terry, and I am happy
I see new faces.
Hi Irene, how
is the operation?
- Well!
- Good. We start walking.
We walk the same spot.
And punch.
Putting bad person.
And punch, punch.
I look up to the knees.
I can see, because the
water is transparent.
Like puppets, and
hand toward the heel.
I am a puppet,
I am a puppet.
On the move by move.
Three other times.
Other two.
And I lied.
Xanaeipa your lies.
I'm as big a liar.
No more.
Come close to the edge of the pool.
Do you know what follows.
We will work away.
Someone pushed to
street, what would you do?
Kick him in the face!
As loud as you can!
Kick him!
Kick, kick!
To hear you say, "Yes!"
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0.
Move away from the edge.
The center.
Come on.
Continue on foot.
Hands in circles.
- Amused?
- Yes!
Hands in circles.
Shoulders. Clapping ...
Shoulders. Clapping.
- We tell everyone, "yes".
- Yes!
- You're not listening!
Now for skiing.
Skiing! Jog ... and shoot.
Push, pull.
Push, pull ...
Go on digging.
Gold! I found gold!
Gold!
Let's make jazz
movements as they walk.
Go.
Yes!
Make my faces jazz.
Persons jazz.
And toggles.
Okay, ladies!
Loop.
I think I'll pee.
No, no!
They put something in the water,
that color.
All out, please!
Soiled the pool.
All out.
Very funny.
Yes, it's very funny.
Pees in the pool.
Not nice, guys.
Not at all.
All out.
Here piss, Margo.
In the shower, like a lady.
It is too
difficult for me,
help myself not to send
All e-mails on this subject.
There was no need to
come with me.
Let us since until
finished the course.
At least manage to
Gymnasts abs.
Sometimes I wonder
whether it makes sense
I shave my legs.
And I'm sure James does not
'll watch anyway.
Why shave my legs?
Love in marriage.
Somewhat depressing.
Sometimes I think,
after 10 years ...
... Who will be interested
whether shave my legs?
At least after both
time I like James.
Worth haggle
do all this ...
Something shocking ...
with someone
that may not be my
like in 10 years?
I do not know.
Sometimes I
just something new.
The new one is shiny.
The new becomes old.
Well, new
become old ...
Just ...
made and old.
I hate you more than
anyone I've ever met
fucking in my life!
Although I do not like to swear
I admit that I hate completely.
I need a drink.
IIt two o'clock.
You sure will
sit in a public place ...
Not ashamed ... after
what did you do in the pool?
Are you completely hated.
Let's get martinis.
- Drink.
- You drink.
First you.
I do not want to get drunk with you.
Impressed with
the consistency you.
I want ...
Do you want ...?
I want to know ...
I want to know what I do.
I said it so simply.
Just like that.
Just kissed the top
of the head.
Too soft ...
- Really?
- Yes.
And then ...
I kissed your eyelids ...
Flickered ... and,
beneath my lips.
- A little.
- A little ...
And ... much too late ...
I touched his lips ...
I with mine.
But because you're married,
I did not dare to kiss.
- No.
Instead, I went
slowly into your throat ...
And ... I kissed every inch of.
And I stopped for a while ...
Sign ... to have
on your left shoulder.
Yeah, that.
And ...
In ... smelled.
Inhale and smell.
How do I smell?
You smell like you.
Like the smell of the plane.
As you smell now.
A mixture ...
Sweetness ... and ...
... Fuck.
And then I kissed your breasts.
And I licked her nipples ...
And stayed there ...
in no time.
And ... I touch you softly
in the beginning, but ...
I understood from the ...
Your reaction to that ..
You do not want ...
I'm gentle.
No?
No.
And then I thought, that
How reacts every point
of her body.
And I worked almost
one and a half week ...
... With your body ...
And ... I started to learn.
And to know.
Each detail.
And ...
I played with you ... ...
Before ... go inside.
Before you open your legs ...
Fuck you ... and loud.
Fuck you harder
than I wanted.
But I could not
to resist.
And I pulled
soft hair ...
And was moving ...
inside you ...
Fuck your mouth ...
Every point ... and you ...
Until we turned ...
so much ...
We could not ...
to see clearly, and ...
I filled in ... with my sperm ...
And ... ...
I told you ... and again
again, "I love you."
I love you.
- These martinis are ...
- Probably unnecessary.
Leave.
One more thing.
Yes.
Because nothing of all this,
not going to happen ...
I close ... one
appointment with you?
What kind of appointment?
An appointment to kiss you.
My program
is very elastic.
It will be in 30 years?
Thirty years?
I'd like to meet
the fountain ...
Lighthouse ... in Louisbourg.
Here I want to meet.
I'm 58 ...
I do not know how you will be.
I'm 59.
I would like to see you there,
this day in ...
2.00 ... 'm m, eastern time.
On August 5, 2040.
And I 'd like to kiss you.
Until then, I'm married.
But after 35 years will
I'm faithful to my husband ...
I think ... I'll have
win a kiss.
I'm going home to clean.
- Hi.
- Do I need to shower.
- Not doing there?
No.
I think I will accept
motion to stay here.
Merry.
Damn it!
Is "katsatore."
Chapter I
the "katsatore" ...
So ... should I make
very "katsatore."
This time I put
chillies.
How do you think you are,
with hot peppers?
I do not care.
Thank you.
Okay, you could ...
Look ... I do not want to fill
Part of gravy, so ..
Okay, seriously now ...
What? Where are you going?
What happened?
You know that you need
courage to do this?
What?
Be to "seduce".
I put all my courage,
And you learn to be
with no courage.
It takes courage to
"Seductions" your husband?
Yes.
He wants all
courage the world.
This is ridiculous.
Is it?
Then why prove it
everything that I'm right?
When I feel that I get
a big risk ...
I prove it ...
everything that I was right ...
And ... that the risk is greater
from what I can manage.
Why ...
Good ... to ...
Talking about ...?
I just cook chicken.
You always cook chicken.
Yes.
I go to the pool.
I must get out.
Scared you fear?
I'm very sorry ...
was a bad idea.
Well ... well ... Yes.
Got it.
Yes ... indeed.
Yes!
No, it makes sense, absolutely.
It has ...
Makes sense ... ...
Okay, okay ...
No, do not do anything ...
No, we do not understand ...
Yes.
Two months Yes,
can be done.
All right.
Very nice, I appreciate it.
Similarly, yes.
Yes ...
Yes ... All right.
Yes.
I did not realize that there was
in this contract.
Merry.
Shall I wait
Yes, I can wait.
What are you doing?
Okay, stop, seriously.
I almost laugh 5 times.
Watch out!
Yes, here I am. Yes ...
I'm not Lin ... sorry ...
Just got my wife.
And wears a funny dress.
- Hi.
Sorry for the pool.
No need to apologize.
I made a nice bathroom.
I gotta go.
All right.
- Today is our anniversary.
- Well. I mean ...
You only know 5
weeks, but I. ..
Want to celebrate ...
anniversaries ...
Gem ... my
an emerald 17 inches.
How long have you been married?
Almost five years.
What does the "man" you?
Why the quotes?
Because the word "spouse"
is funny.
Writes cookbooks.
Cookbooks?
Books for chickens ...
Books for cooking chicken ...
Books ... how to
cook the chicken.
Only chicken?
Yes, only.
- Eating too chicken?
- You can not imagine!
But it is a very good cook.
If you like chicken.
Do you like chicken?
Naturally. When it is cooked.
The house always smells
nicely when cooked ...
Only ... the smell of garbage
chicken is disgusting.
Hi!
What's up
Daniel, from now Lou.
Is our neighbor.
Fine! Now you come here?
Lately. There.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Begin? If we leave
Now, you make it.
Where are you going
It's our anniversary.
Every time we go to see
a movie at Royal.
Nicely.
Climb up, you go too.
No, never mind.
We anticipate walk.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, of course.
I always wanted to climb
in one of them!
Perfect!
Really?
Really, yes.
Come on, what are you doing? Come.
We have some time.
Will you go with
rickshaw, climb!
Get in, is
the anniversary you.
Come! Do it.
What are you doing? Through Bess.
What the heck?
We'll go ride rickshaw!
- Come on!
- A leptaki.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Are you ready?
This is a historic moment.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
God.
Plate has!
All right.
Thank you very much.
How many ...
How much we owe you ...?
- It's on the house.
- No!
Maybe with cherries
chicken, someday.
Margo told you about ...
Yes, of course.
Would like very much.
I need a new audience.
Margo has taken too
dose of chicken anymore.
Not true.
- Thank you very much.
- Please.
- Have fun.
- Goodbye.
Well ...
Yes?
How are things going?
Merry. What do you mean?
I mean ... I do not know ...
Say something ...
Why
To open a conversation.
I have to say something.
This is a good sign.
I will not say anything, just
open to debate.
Why not ask me how am I doing?
Because I know how you doing.
I do not know?
Yeah, I guess. Just ...
You do not seem a bit strange,
we sit here
without talking?
And what can we say?
We live together, we know everything
about each other.
Then what is the point
go out for dinner?
To eat good food.
To go to a beautiful place.
Not to say our newsletter.
Come here, come on.
I love you.
It is the anniversary
we love you.
Happy birthday.
I love you.
Hey.
Now who is watching whom?
- I met my husband.
- Indeed.
How was your anniversary?
Was okay.
Okay?
Yes. It ...
It is the most good and
polite person in the world.
It seemed sweet.
Seemed to be very loving.
And I love him.
This came to tell me?
You love your husband, and
The anniversary was okay?
Why was it okay?
I feel that there is no
greatest betrayal ...
From ... to complain
for my husband to ...
In whom?
Come take a ride.
I want to go out in the world with you.
Can we?
We can move
day together?
Please?
Yes.
Let's do it.
Have you ever been to the Flyers
carts at amusement parks?
It is dark and
play music ...
Going ... and very quickly
to do something stupid.
- See you.
- Sometime.
- Soon.
- I guess.
- Hi.
- What will you do now?
- Nothing.
You must do
something, not me.
I gotta say it again, that
I'm in love with you?
I do not have it said before.
In this case ...
Nothing?
I can not!
I can not ...
I think we should
Now go home, Margo.
- What?
- I do not know.
These here ...
I have blackheads?
I woke up, and you know when you have
one that has just come out ...
And you can ...
to see it yet ...
I think there is.
I love you.
The good thing of not being completely
dedicated to AA, is ...
That ... friends and relatives, your
make a great party with drinks ...
To celebrate ...
the poise you ...
Which is ...
totally inappropriate ...
And ... absolutely fantastic.
Well ...
Pick up the bottle ... about ...
(Carbonated water)
Cheers ... to all of you who
you can become a fez
without guilt ...
The imaginary brother ...
me and my sister ...
I brought ... more
a neat piece cake ...
Wonderful ... to my children, who
is not here, Tony ...
... I thank you for tolerating
the worst year ...
And lovely ...
My husband, James ...
James not to say?
Who confided ... enough
to be with
you drunk assholes.
Enough of this shit ...
Put your music ...
to dance, assholes!
- Lou!
- Hey, I did not expect to come ...
Lost ... why.
It was perfect.
You ashtray? Fine.
Come out of here, have a drink.
- Never mind, I ...
- Come on!
A drink!
Basically I have a job ...
It's Saturday night.
Be a good neighbor!
Fuck!
Merry.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Yes.
You say hello to Daniel?
Yes, you can not imagine
whether he be persuaded to come.
- Want some kebab?
- Yes, for the book.
- To get no beer.
- Yes, they are out.
- What do you think?
- Delicious!
Thank you.
- Interesting choice!
- I tried not to come.
He insisted much.
Something tells me it could
to find an excuse.
I was thinking that this fear
you got to airports.
Being in between ...
I think me
I do not like.
I know that it is in
nature of life, but ...
D like to ... avoid,
where possible.
I do not think I want to
I'm in between.
You must go to the party.
- You can stay as long as you want.
- I will not stay long.
You're leaving already?
Good luck with
chicken, man.
Thank you.
August 5, 2040. 2.00-m m
Lou?
I do not think ... I do not think ...
Gosh, I do not know ...
I thought you were
there when you die ...
Do not say that!
What the heck does that mean?
I think somewhere I knew that
something was amiss, and ...
Just hoping ... that will
left alone.
You are so beautiful!
And I feel that
I never deserved ...
No, no!
I feel that ...
I beg you ... if you stay,
will humiliate ...
In high school I was with someone ...
Lost ... one testicle
a hockey game ...
And ... I'm sure that had
design very different life ...
From ... it finally did.
At least I've
my testicles.
Maybe you ought to have a bath.
It makes you feel better.
I do not want to bathe.
Just ...
... Do me a favor, okay?
You?
Yes.
- Every ...?
- Every day.
There ...?
No problem
water ...
Or ... something has to be corrected
I just thought ...
One day I'll tell the Margo ...
That ... I do
throughout her life ...
And ... will make you laugh.
It's funny "long-term".
RETURN ON HEARING:
CALAMITY JANE
(With the precious help of Remedy!)
Go.
Fuck.
Here you are.
I love you.
I love you!
"He chicken flavor."
Glad we did not expect.
Me too.
Hello?
- Hi.
- Hey, Margo.
The Tony wanted to tell
"Hello" Say "hello", Tony.
Hey!
In pethymisa, theioula Margo.
And I in pethymisa.
Okay, now we
I'm going to eat, bye.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
The Geraldine disappeared, and
Tony is left alone ...
For hours ... ...
James shouted ...
the police ...
Say ... and will go
within a few hours ...
I do not know what
I here ...
I do not think
I stay ...
My God ...
- Madam Verok ...
- Okay, one leptaki ...
Madam, we would like to
join us.
Jerry, you must go
with him, okay?
One minute.
Geraldine, go
with them, darling.
We'll be here when you get back.
Okay, one leptaki, Mom.
Look, James, I got birds.
It takes ... milk. I think ...
What
For Tony, I got to
Shop pets.
There is ...
Margo!
You're back?
- I missed you!
- Okay, lady.
I have a leptaki?
I need to talk
this lady.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I want to see you too long.
Too long.
This needs to
back? What're you doing?
What happened, Geraldine?
I am an alcoholic, stupid.
Nothing happened.
This is the normal
my situation.
What happened ... seriously?
Why should not I ask you?
You disappeared, just like that.
What an obvious move, damn it!
Do you believe that everything can be solved
if you do just the right move?
It should be exciting.
I think it is exciting.
I do not agree.
Do not! Do not do it.
I bring you in
embarrassed? Ego?
You know I do
same thing here, damn it?
I do not understand what
trying to say.
I think you're more
silly me.
I think you're really
very confused, Margo.
In the general picture ...
Life is empty and no
we are just us.
Do not go crazy to
fillings, like no daredevil.
I must go, damn.
Okay, let's go.
It was fun.
It's hard to talk ...
Honestly ... with people
when you have not drunk ...
Thing ... I'm sure
you can imagine, Captain.
Jumped last
no harlot?
- Break any head?
- Get in the car, please.
You see, it's fun.
I will drive?
Sorry.
The Tony wanted in here, and
I did not know what to do ...
Jerry ... and in
had pethymisei.
No, no, never mind.
I should have phoned.
We just do not know what to say.
It is difficult to
You know, I guess.
How are you?
Merry. Basically, unexpectedly ...
Finally ... ... All right.
In the book you
went very well.
Really, did you see?
Thanks, I know.
Who would expect that like
both the chicken in the world?
And with so many
ways of cooking.
We'll see how it goes
the second book.
You write the second book?
No, do not be silly.
It is for the hens N.
Guinea and pheasants.
- Yes?
- No, idiot.
How is your life?
- You mean if I go with no?
- No!
I do not want to ... Yes.
Sometimes.
No, actually not.
Do you ever think ...?
No, I think not.
I think not.
You said that there
going out with no ...
Some things you do
in your life, much ...
- Sorry ...
- There is no reason to be sad ...
... How can you be sad because
you did what you had to do?
But I did not think that ...
We did not do it
this discussion ...
Frankly I do not care ...
to do now.
Naturally. Sorry. Got it.
I'm sorry too.
Will me, if I
to do something for Tony,
or Jerry or ... for you?
Yes, I think we
we are okay.
Goodbye.
Margo!
Yes.
I just bought a machine
make melon balls ...
And ... I'd like to
I take out the eyes with it.
Yeah, me too.
Bye, Margo.
Goodbye, Lou.0